<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">RailsBridge Chicago</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="" />
<updated>2015-03-02T16:06:32-06:00</updated>
<id>/</id>
<author>
  <name>RailsBridge Chicago</name>
  <uri>/</uri>
  <email>railsbridgechi@gmail.com</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello RailsBridge]]></title>
  <link>/news/first-commit</link>
  <id>/news/first-commit</id>
  <published>2015-01-16T00:00:00-06:00</published>
  <updated>2015-01-16T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>RailsBridge Chicago</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>railsbridgechi@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&quot;It’s all happening!&quot;
&lt;small&gt;&lt;cite title=&quot;Plato&quot;&gt;Me&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s up y’all, we have a blooooorg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing some stuff here.  It’s great!  Commence the “Whedon Ipsum”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- start whedon ipsum --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a real burn, being right so often. I’ve got four brothers, none of them Democrats. We need to save Buffy from Hansel and Gretel. I was actually at Woodstock. That was a weird gig. I fed off a flower person, and then I spent the next six hours watching my hand move. Seems odd you’d name your ship after a battle you were on the wrong side of. And what’s with all the carrots?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last month he’s the freak with jicama breath who waxes his back. First of all, Feng Shui up the yin yang, also I designed parts of it but I did not design the stone cold foxes in the small clothes and the ample massage facilities. Why can’t you just masturbate like the rest of us? Bunnies! Bunnies! It must be Bunnies! With any luck, he’ll poke the wrong one and end up in an alternative dimension inhabited by a fifty-foot Giles that squishes annoying teeny pirates. It’s just a long cultural tradition of raging insincerity. It has nothing to do with me. Some terrifying space monkeys maybe got loose?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t have wings, we just skate around with perfect hair fighting crime. In the time of gods and monsters, what is the worth of a man? So I skipped intro to evil or whatever, but how is it that I get an F, when this guy that we’re reading, Chauncey, can’t even spell? The gentlemen are coming by. How did your brain even learn human speech? I’m just so curious. Say Skywalker, and I smack ya. It’s funny how the Earth never opens up and swallows you when you want it to. You will keep a civil tongue in this house or we’ll put your tongue in a stew.
&lt;!-- please do not remove this line --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;display:none;&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.commercekitchen.com&quot;&gt;ipsum generator&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- end whedon ipsum code --&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/news/first-commit&quot;&gt;Hello RailsBridge&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by RailsBridge Chicago at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;RailsBridge Chicago&lt;/a&gt; on January 16, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>

</feed>
